Call us at 1-877-446-7746

Shop by category Categories

Main Menu

Close the main menu

Search

Close Search

Please enter content and submit to complete search

Privacy Policy
==============

This policy describes the information we may collect, how we may collect and use it, and certain other privacy issues, including the precautions we take to protect your privacy.

Our policy covers the following topics:
---------------------------------------

* [Section D - Review and Correction of Personally Identifiable Information](#secD)

Scope and Purpose of this Policy
--------------------------------

This policy applies to any individual who accesses our online presences and provides any type or amount of personal information. Personal information, in general, is information that is linked or reasonably linkable to a natural person. The purpose of this policy is to explain how and what personal information we collect, how we use this information, and to express our commitment to protecting your privacy.

Section A: Information Collected and How it is Used
---------------------------------------------------

Please note that we collect and store certain limited information related to your visits and interactions with our site. What we collect and how we use it is set forth below.

### What we collect when you browse our site:

If you do nothing during your visit but browse, read content, or download information, we will gather and store certain limited information about your visit. We automatically collect and store the following information about your visit:

1. Your IP address, which is an identifier assigned either to your internet service or directly to your computer. We use the IP address to direct internet traffic to you;
2. Your browsing behavior, which includes your browser and device characteristics;
3. The date and time you visited;
4. The pages or services you accessed; and
5. Any referring URLs, or sites that directed you to our site.

The information we automatically collect or store is not personally identifiable information ([see Section B](#secB)), and used by us only for improving the content of our site services and to help us understand how people are using our services so that we may continually improve the performance, suitability and usefulness of our sites to you, our customers and potential customers.

### What else we collect if you provide it to us:

If, during your visit, you participate in a survey, send an e-mail, or perform some other transaction ([see Section C](#secC)) on-line, we will have collected the following information (some of which may be personally identifiable) in addition to information listed above:

1. The e-mail address, and contents of e-mail, for those who communicate with us via e-mail;
2. The contents of chats, for those who communicate with us via live chats with a 4imprint representative;
3. Information volunteered in response to a survey or by participating in a contest or other promotion sponsored by us;
4. Information volunteered during your registration on our site; and
5. Information volunteered through an on-line form for any other purpose, including requests to receive samples or marketing information, credit applications (for businesses), subscriptions to our newsletter or other content, and use of our on-line order forms to order products or services.

We will use your e-mail to respond appropriately. This may be to respond to you or to address issues you may identify, and as a means to further improve our services or site. If you have an account with us, we will also use this information for marketing and promotions, to launch product surveys, and as an added service to you to pre-populate on-line order forms to save you time in the ordering and re-ordering process.

All of the information we collected is retained as long as legally required or for as long as necessary for legitimate business purposes, whichever is longer.

### Use and disclosure of information collected:

Please note that there are instances where we share your volunteered information with other parties for legitimate business purposes in connection with processing your order.

4IMPRINT, like many internet and catalog retailers, employs other companies and individuals to perform specific functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivery of packages, mail and e-mail, address hygiene, credit card processing services, or research that improves the quality of services or offers provided to you. These providers have access only to the information that they require to perform their functions but are contractually prohibited by us from using that information for any other purposes. You may, however, “opt-out” of this use of your information at any time, but doing so may impair our ability to provide you with proper service and to process your orders ([see Section K](#secK)).

We may disclose your name and mailing address to other carefully-screened parties for marketing purposes. However, we never share your e-mail address, phone number, credit card or financial information for these purposes.

Please refer to [see Section L](#secL) for additional notifications and information that we collect, disclose, and sell.

Section B: Personally Identifiable Information and Choice
---------------------------------------------------------

You may always choose whether to provide personal information to us on-line.

Personal information, in general, is information that is linked or reasonably linkable to a natural person. Personal information includes such things as an individual’s name, address, and phone number. As noted above ([see Section A](#secA)), none of your personal information is collected automatically when you access our site; personal information is only collected by us when you voluntarily provide it to us.

You may always choose not to contact us by e-mail, participate in a survey or to provide any personal information using an on-line form. Alternative methods for contacting us in person, by phone or by mail are available by using the information in the Contact Information section at the end of this policy ([see Section K](#secK)). Your choice to not participate in these activities on-line will not impair your ability to browse, read or download content provided via the site.

In the event we are required to respond to a subpoena, court order or other legal process, your personal information may be disclosed pursuant to such subpoena, court order or other legal process, which may be without notice to you.

Section C: Transaction Information
----------------------------------

If you request any information, buy any products or subscribe to any services offered by us via our site, we will ask you to complete an order form that requires certain information, including payment information such as a credit card number and expiration date as well as general contact, billing and shipping information. This information is necessary to complete the transaction and to deliver to you the information, products or services ordered and to collect payment.

The credit card information that you provide to us will be provided to the credit card issuing company to complete your transaction, and 4imprint makes no assurances or representations about the use of your information by these third parties. For your protection, all such information is collected, and all credit card information is stored by 4imprint via encrypted means.

Section D: Review and Correction of Personally Identifiable Information
-----------------------------------------------------------------------

You can contact us about the any personally identifiable information we collect about you by using the information below (which is also in the Contact Information section at the end of this policy ([see Section K](#secK))). You may recommend changes to your personally identifiable information you believe to be inaccurate by submitting an e-mail or written request that credibly shows the inaccuracy. We will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

If your personal information changes, you may correct, update or remove the personal data you have provided to us by making changes to your profile. In addition, you may opt-out of certain communications from us ([see Section K](#secK)). Our goal is to make sure that our information about you is always current so that we can better serve you.

### Contact Information

[\[email protected\]](https://www.4imprint.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  
101 Commerce Street  
Oshkosh, WI 54901 USA  
1-877-520-2006

Section E: Cookies, Interest-Based Advertising and Opt-Outs
-----------------------------------------------------------

To serve our on-line users, we use "cookies" and other technologies to passively collect demographic information, customize your browsing experience with us, personalize your experience on our site and monitor advertisements and other activities. Cookies are small data files transferred to your computer by your web browser. We use the cookies feature only to store a randomly generated identifying tag on your computer or electronic device.

Currently, our systems do not recognize browser "do-not-track" requests. You may, however, disable certain tracking by disabling cookies in your browser. However, if you disable cookies, your experience on our website may be affected.

Although we don’t use cookies to collect or share information with third parties to deliver advertisements online referred to as Interest-based or behavioral advertising, you can learn more about those types of advertising and how to set your preferences (opt-out) here: [Find out more about your options opens in new window.](https://thenai.org/about-online-advertising/faq/?tab=3)

Section F: Electronic Communication
-----------------------------------

When you access our site or send e-mails to us, you are communicating with us electronically and consenting to receive communications from us electronically. We will communicate with you by e-mail or by posting notices via our site. To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive confirmation when you open e-mail from us if your computer supports such capabilities. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, email [\[email protected\]](https://www.4imprint.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or find additional ways to [contact us here](https://www.4imprint.com/info/contactus).

Section G: Security and Social Media
------------------------------------

We safeguard the integrity of our site with measures designed and intended to prevent the corruption of data and to block unknown or unauthorized access to our systems and information. However, it is important to recognize that whatever you transmit or disclose online could be collected and used by others or even unlawfully intercepted by third parties. No data transmission over the internet can ever be guaranteed to be 100% secure and by transmitting your data in this matter you agree to release 4imprint from any liability for damages incurred as a result of transmission. While we strive to protect your information, we cannot warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us.

You may also take steps of your own to protect your information. For example, you should create a unique, quality password and not share that password with others or use it on any other website. You should not leave your computer or electronic device unattended before exiting a session and prior to logging out. You should also properly exit browsers as you move between websites. Please see the [4imprint Legal Statement](https://www.4imprint.com/info/legalstatement) for additional details.

Section H: A Special Note for Parents
-------------------------------------

Our website is not designed to normally collect information on and/or from minors. While our site is intended for general audiences, it is possible that minors will access the site and certain information automatically collected ([see Section A](#secA)). However, we will never knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13). If we receive any information from persons we believe to be minors, it will be purged from our database in accordance with any applicable laws.

Section I: Disclaimer - Links to Other Sites
--------------------------------------------

This policy applies only to the 4IMPRINT sites. Although our site may provide links to other sites, including but not limited to, social media sites where 4IMPRINT may utilize an account on the platform, be advised that 4IMPRINT is not responsible for the content of such other sites and is not liable for any damages or injury arising from that content. Any links are provided merely as a convenience to our users. When you link to another site, you are no longer on a 4IMPRINT site and this privacy policy will not apply. When you link to a site, you are subject to, and should consult, the privacy policy of that site, and particularly before providing any personal information.

Section J: Revision
-------------------

We may at any time revise the terms and conditions contained in this privacy policy by updating this posting. Accordingly, you should periodically visit this page to review our current privacy policy.

Section K: Contact Information and Enforcement
----------------------------------------------

To correct your personal information, to send an “opt-out” message, or if you have questions or concerns about 4IMPRINT’s privacy policy, you may contact 4IMPRINT as follows:

### Contact Information

[\[email protected\]](https://www.4imprint.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  
101 Commerce Street  
Oshkosh, WI 54901 USA  
1-877-520-2006

Section L: Consumer Notifications
---------------------------------

This section provides information required under applicable state privacy laws, including information about how we use personal information, whether collected online or offline, and this document is intended to satisfy those requirements. This section does not address or apply to our handling of publicly available information lawfully made available by state or federal government records or other personal information that is exempt under the law.

For purposes of this section, “personal information” is any information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular individual or household.

### Categories of Personal Information that We Collect, Disclose, and Sell

While our collection, use and disclosure of personal information varies based upon our relationship and interactions with you, in this section we describe, generally, how we collect and disclose personal information about consumers. As further described in the “Information Collected and How It is Used” section above ([see Section A](#secA)), we may collect personal information from the following sources:

* directly from the individual
* advertising networks and partners
* event sponsors
* data analytics providers
* social networks
* operating systems and platforms
* government entities
* business customers
* service providers

#### Do Not Sell Option.

You can exercise your right to opt-out of our sale of your personal information by email using [\[email protected\]](https://www.4imprint.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or by visiting our [preference manager online opens in new window](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/ec3f514a-eaab-4cff-bad7-d1035ad359ff/86317488-1e65-4d95-a299-850abb6cdcb9).

#### Specific Category Information

Below please find the categories of personal information about consumers that we collect, sell, and/or disclose to third parties or service providers for a business purpose. Under the law, a “sale” includes disclosing or making available to a third-party personal information, in exchange for monetary compensation or some other value or benefit.

While we do not disclose personal information in exchange for monetary compensation, we may make certain categories of personal information available in order to receive certain benefits or services. In the table below where we have indicated that we sell information, we do so to support our direct mail marketing programs.

The information allows us and other advertisers to better identify potential customers to market to. Other advertisers only receive the information noted: the ‘NAME’ ‘CONTACT INFORMATION AND IDENTIFIERS’ ‘PURCHASE HISTORY’ and ‘PRODUCT CATEGORY’ section of the ‘Categories of Personal Information’ below.

| Categories of Personal Information | Do we collect? | Do we disclose for business purposes? | Do we sell? | Categories of Other Entities to Whom We May Disclose or Sell this Information |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
| NAME, CONTACT INFORMATION AND IDENTIFIERS: Identifiers such as a real name, alias, company name, postal address. | YES | YES | YES | * Advisors and agents<br>* Data analytics providers<br>* Direct mail list cooperatives and brokers<br>* Entities for legal purpose<br>* Entities that may acquire our business or assets<br>* Operating systems and platforms<br>* Service providers |
| OTHER IDENTIFIERS: Identifiers such as email address, unique personal identifier, online personal identifiers, Internet Protocol (IP) address | YES | YES | NO  | * Data analytics providers<br>* Entities for legal purpose<br>* Entities that may acquire our business or assets<br>* Operating systems and platforms<br>* Service providers |
| CUSTOMER RECORDS: Paper and electronic customer records containing personal information, such as name, signature, address, telephone number, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information – note that most of our business is B2B. | YES | YES | NO  | * Data analytics providers<br>* Entities for legal purpose<br>* Entities that may acquire our business or assets<br>* Operating systems and platforms<br>* Service providers |
| PURCHASE HISTORY AND PRODUCT CATEGORY INTERESTS: Commercial information, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming tendencies. | YES | YES | YES | * Advisors and Agents<br>* Data analytics providers<br>* Direct mail list cooperatives and brokers<br>* Entities for legal purpose<br>* Entities that acquire our business or assets<br>* Operating systems and platforms<br>* Service providers |
| USAGE DATA: Internet or other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing history, search history, and information regarding a resident’s interaction with an internet website, application, or advertisement. | YES | YES | NO  | * Data analytics providers<br>* Entities for legal purpose<br>* Entities that may acquire our business or assets<br>* Operating systems and platforms<br>* Service providers |
| AUDIO/VISUAL: Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information. | NO  | NO  | NO  | N/A |
| EMPLOYMENT HISTORY: Professional or employment-related information. | NO  | NO  | NO  | N/A |
| EDUCATION INFORMATION: Information that is not publicly available personally identifiable information as defined in the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (20 U.S.C. section 1232g, 34 C.F.R. Part 99). | NO  | NO  | NO  | N/A |
| PROFILES AND INFERENCES: Inferences drawn from any of the information identified above to create a profile about a resident reflecting the resident’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes. | NO  | NO  | NO  | N/A |

### SENSITIVE PERSONAL DATA

| Categories of Personal Information | Do we collect? | Do we disclose for business purposes? | Do we sell? | Categories of Other Entities to Whom We May Disclose or Sell this Information |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
| BIOMETRIC INFORMATION: Physiological, biological or behavioral characteristics that can be used alone or in combination with each other to establish individual identity, including DNA, imagery of the iris, retina, fingerprint, face, hand, palm, vein patterns, and voice recordings, keystroke patterns or rhythms, gait patterns or rhythms, and sleep, health, or exercise data that contain identifying information. | NO  | NO  | NO  | N/A |
| GEOLOCATION DATA: Precise geographic location information about a particular individual or device. | NO  | NO  | NO  | N/A |
| PROTECTED CLASSIFICATIONS: Characteristics of legally protected classifications such as race, color, sex, age, religion, national origin, disability, citizenship status, and genetic information. | NO  | NO  | NO  | N/A |

### Your Rights

Right to Opt-out. You have the right to opt out of our sale of your personal information. Opt-out rights can be exercised by email using [\[email protected\]](https://www.4imprint.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or by visiting our [preference manager online opens in new window](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/ec3f514a-eaab-4cff-bad7-d1035ad359ff/86317488-1e65-4d95-a299-850abb6cdcb9).

Right to Opt-in. We do not collect or sell personal information about individuals who we know are younger than 16 years old without opt-in consent.

Right to Rectify. You have the right to request that we correct personal information we’ve collected about you that is inaccurate.

Right to Restrict. You have the right to limit our use or disclosure of sensitive personal information collected about you.

Right to Know. You have the right to request that we provide you certain information about how we have handled your personal information in the prior 12 months (up to twice per year and subject to certain exemptions), including the:

* categories of personal information collected;
* categories of sources of personal information;
* business and/or commercial purposes for collecting and selling their personal information;
* categories of third parties/with whom we have disclosed for a business purpose or sold their personal information;
* categories of personal information that we have disclosed for a business purpose or sold; and
* a copy of the specific pieces of personal information that we have collected about them.

Submitting Requests. Requests to exercise the foregoing rights may be submitted by email using [\[email protected\]](https://www.4imprint.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or by visiting our [preference manager online opens in new window](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/ec3f514a-eaab-4cff-bad7-d1035ad359ff/86317488-1e65-4d95-a299-850abb6cdcb9). We will respond to verifiable requests received as required by law.

In addition, you may opt of “sales” of your personal information by us by emailing us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.4imprint.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or by using our [preference manager online opens in new window](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/ec3f514a-eaab-4cff-bad7-d1035ad359ff/86317488-1e65-4d95-a299-850abb6cdcb9).

When you submit a request to us, we will take steps to verify your request by matching the information provided by you with the information we have in our records. You must complete all required fields on our webform (or otherwise provide us with this information via the above email address) to verify your request.

In some cases, we may request additional information in order to verify your request or where necessary to process your request. If we are unable to adequately verify your request, we will notify you.

Authorized agents may initiate a request on behalf of another individual by contacting us online at the above link or by email using [\[email protected\]](https://www.4imprint.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection); authorized agents will be required to provide proof of their authorization and we may also require that the relevant consumer directly verify their identity and the authority of the authorized agent.

Right to Non-Discrimination, and Incentives. The law prohibits discrimination against individuals for exercising their rights under the law and imposes requirements on any financial incentives offered to individuals related to their personal information. We do not offer any incentives at this time.

For more information about our privacy practices, you may contact us as set forth in the [Section K](#secK) Contact Us section above.

### California Privacy Rights under California’s Shine-the-Light Law

Under California’s “Shine the Light” law (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.83), California residents who provide us certain personal information are entitled to request and obtain from us, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we have shared with third parties for their own direct marketing use. Such requests may be made once per calendar year for information about any relevant third party sharing in the prior calendar year. California residents who would like to make such a request may submit a request by email using [\[email protected\]](https://www.4imprint.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). The request should attest to the fact that the requester is a California resident and provide a current California address.

Need Help?
----------

Our 360°  
Guarantee®
---------------------

means you're covered from every angle.

* Certain delivery. It's on time or it's on us.
* Certain value. Or we'll refund double the difference.
* Certain happiness. If you're not 100% satisfied, we'll refund or rerun.

### See why 4imprint is the best promotional products value in America.

[watch  
video about why you should buy from 4imprint](https://www.4imprint.com/info/whybuyfromus?v=play#videoContainer)

### Corporate

### Media

### Services

### Worldwide

From Fortune. © 2024, Fortune Media IP Limited All rights reserved. Used under license.  
Fortune and Fortune Media IP Limited are not affiliated with, and do not endorse products or services of, 4imprint.  
People Companies That Care Logo is used under license, © 2022, TI Gotham, Inc.

Shopping at 4imprint is secure and 100% guaranteed  
© 1994 - 2024 4imprint Inc. All rights reserved. [Legal information](https://www.4imprint.com/info/legalstatement).  
Glide is protected by U.S. Pat. No. 7,979,318  
Here's some stuff you don't need to know, but we do!  
aw0mdwk0004A6
